A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, United States Program, Accession 2007:077, SG 2 FA1131
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, United States Program, Accession 2007:077, SG 2
1983-2007
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1131
14.15 Cubic Feet 36 letter-sized document boxes, 1 legal document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accession digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
The material in this collection documents the work of The Commonwealth Fund's United States Program from the late 1990s through 2004/2005, although some material dates from as early as 1983 and as late as 2007. Grants comprise the bulk of the material.
Biographical / Historical
The Commonwealth Fund was founded in 1918 by Mrs. Stephen (Anna) Harkness with the mandate that it should "do something for the welfare of mankind". Most of the Fund's grants throughout its existence have been in the broad field of health. Over the years, The Commonwealth Fund's work led to the development of the field of child guidance, contributed to the emergence of progressive public health departments in communities throughout the country, supported the construction of rural hospitals, and supported the development of new medical schools in the United States. Several facets of the Fund's continued interest in health are seen in this collection, including the availability of quality medical education and the Fund's concern for the "underserved" or vulnerable populations among us – including women, children, minority populations, those in urban areas, the elderly, and the financially disadvantaged.
Arrangement
The material in this collection is divided into four series: Academic Health Centers, Medicare's Future, Quality of Care for Underserved Populations, and Program Officer Grant Files. The arrangement reflects the original order in which the material was received.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The material in this collection was received from the Treasurer's Office of The Commonwealth Fund. The individuals responsible for placing this material at the RAC were Diana Davenport and Tammy Ziccardi. The records were transferred to RAC in 2007 and officially accessioned as Accession 2007:077.
- Academic Health Centers
  - Academic Health Centers-1983 Task Force (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Health Centers-Proposal, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Background on Academic Health Centers Task Force, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New York City Academic Health Centers, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - MGH/Blumenthal Board Book Write ups: 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    General
    EMPTY FOLDER
  - AHC Overviews: 1997 and 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AHC Program Plans, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7-8, Box 2, Folder 9-13)
  - AHC Board Presentation: July 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Agenda Drafts and Correspondence on Fall 2001 AHC Task Force Meeting and Forum (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Assessment of Changing Status of AHC Missions: Massachusetts General Hospital/Blumenthal: Proposal Development (#20000340), 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - AHC Faculty Rnd II (Commonwealth) Respondent Excel spreadsheet (pewfac.ZIP), 2016:FA1131:001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers Support for Program Direction and Analysis, 2001-02: Massachusetts General Hospital/David Blumenthal (#20010699), 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 17-24, Box 4, Folder 25-26, 28)
  - "International Challenges for Academic Medicine? A Comparative Study of Academic Health Organizations in the UK and the USA", Stephen Davies, Institute for Health Policy/Academic Health Centers Fund Publication, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Program Report on AHC Program: Michael McGarvey (#20020241-PDF), 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 29-32)
  - University Governing Board Responsibilities for Governance of AHC's: Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges/Thomas Longin (#20030145-PDF), 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
- Medicare's Future
  - Medicare Program Plans, 1999-2003 (Box 5, Folder 35, 40-41, Box 6, Folder 44)
  - State Health Insurance Assistance Programs: Training Manual for Dual Eligible Programs: January 2000 (Box 5, Folder 36-38)
  - State Health Insurance Assistance Programs: Update to January 2000 Training Manual for Dual Eligible Programs: March 2000 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Medicare Discretionary Grants Completed Between 9/1/2001 and 6/30/2002 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Meetings (2002) including Program Monitoring Committee Meeting of September 5, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Medicare Program Review: April 2003 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Medicare Brainstorming Meeting: May 17, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Medicare-Program Plan: Update on Grants Process: June 1, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Medicare-Program Plan: Main Meeting: June 9, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Primary Care Development Corporation Research Study: September 2006 (Box 6, Folder 49, Box 7, Folder 50-53)
  - Survey of Low-Income Elderly Living at Home: Johns Hopkins University/Judith Kasper (#980510), 1987, 1996-2002 (Box 7, Folder 54-55, Box 8, Folder 56-62)
  - Medicare Rights Center/Diane Archer (#980600), 1997-2001 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Medicare Beneficiaries and Prescription Drug Coverage in New York: Margaret Davis/Mount Sinai School of Medicine (#20000818-PDF), 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 64-65)
  - Survey of Low-Income Elderly about State Publicly Funded Prescription Drug Assistance: Dana Safran/New England Medical Center (#20010182), 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 66-70, Box 10, Folder 71-72)
  - New York Supplement to Medicare Beneficiaries: New England Medical Center/Dana Safran (#20010442), 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Coverage, Access, and Use of Prescription Drugs by the Disabled: Bruce Stuart/University of Maryland (#20010482-PDF), 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Appropriate Drug Use and Prescription Drug Insurance Programs: Adding Value by Improving Quality: Jacqueline Eng/U.S. Pharmacopeia (#20010563-PDF), 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - BenefitsCheckUp: Helping Low-Income Seniors Receive Health and Other Benefits, Phase One: National Council on the Aging/James Firman (#20010613), 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 76-80)
  - Developing a Coordinated Care Benefit in Traditional Medicare: A National Conference: Center for Medicare Advocacy/Judith Stein (#20020004), 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 81-82)
  - Examining the Cost and Quality of Prescription Drug Coverage for Medicare Beneficiaries, Phase Two: University of Maryland/Bruce Stuart (#20020096), 2001-2004 (Box 11, Folder 83-87)
  - New Cost Estimates for a Medicare Prescription Drug Benefit: University of Maryland/Bruce Stuart (#20020103), 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Health Policy Seminars and Congressional Staff Retreat: Alliance for Health Reform/Edward Howard (#20020158), 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Maximizing the Use of the BenefitsCheckUp Database: National Council on the Aging/Nancy Whitelaw (#20020175), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Pharmaceutical Benefit Manager (PBM) Appeals Processes and Their Implications for a Medicare Drug Benefit: Georgetown University/Michael Gluck (#20020201), 2001-2003 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Medicare's Future: Support for Program Direction and Policy Analysis: Urban Institute/Marilyn Moon (#20020455), 2001-2003 (Box 12, Folder 92-95)
  - High Tech-High Touch: Making the Connections to Improve Medicine Use for Older Adults: University of Maryland/Bruce Stuart (#20020542), 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Quality Improvement in Medicare (formerly Mount Sinai/Commonwealth Seminar Series on Medicare): Mount Sinai Medical Center/Bruce Vladeck (#20020552), 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Medicare Managed Care: Trends in Benefits and Premiums, 2003-2004: Mathematica Policy Research, Inc./Marsha Gold (#20020646), 2000-2004 (Box 13, Folder 98-102)
  - National and State Surveys of Prescription Drug Coverage and Costs Among Medicare Beneficiaries: New England Medical Center Hospitals, Inc./Dana Safran (#20020740), 2002-2005 (Box 13, Folder 103-106, Box 14, Folder 107-112, Box 15, Folder 113-114)
  - BenefitsCheckUp: Helping Low Income Seniors Receive Health and Other Benefits, Phase Two: National Council on the Aging/James Firman (#20030093), 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 115-118)
  - BenefitsCheckUp: A valuable service for older Americans - General Promotional Edition, VHS; 8 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11747)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - BenefitsCheckUp: Volunteers Outreach - 3/7/03, 2003 March 7; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11748)
  - 2003 Health Policy Seminars and Congressional Staff Retreat: Alliance for Health Reform/Edward Howard (#20030146), 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 119-122)
  - Administrative Changes to Improve Medicare: Addressing Beneficiary Concerns: Medicare Rights Center/Robert Hayes (#20030374), 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 123-125)
  - Program Direction Grant for Fund's Program on Medicare's Future: Georgetown College/Barbara Cooper (#20031424), 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - Health Insurance Experiences of Older Americans Before and After Enrolling in Medicare: International Communications Research/Melissa Herrmann (#20040176), 1999, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 127-132)
  - 2004 Health Policy Seminars and Congressional Staff Retreat: Alliance for Health Reform/Edward Howard (#20040178), 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 133-134)
- Quality of Care for Underserved Populations
  - Minority Health Program Overview: "Bettering the Health of Minority Americans: Opportunities and Concerns in a Changing Health Care System", Brian Biles and Karen Scott Collins, April 14, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - Minority Health Program: Advisory Committee Meetings, 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 136-139)
  - Managed Care and Minority Communities: Program Plan: November 1997 (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - Commonwealth Fund Minority Program History: "A Commitment to Leadership: The Commonwealth Fund's History of Supporting Equality and Minority Health Care", Karen Davis, Karen Scott Collins, Charlotte Neuhaus, Draft, December 10, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - BHMA: Program Plan: February 1999 (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - Minority Health Overview Issue Brief, November-December 2000 (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - Minority Fellowships by Other Funders, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations: Program Plans, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 145-149)
  - Minority Health Policy Fellowship Program Plans, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 150-151, Box 18, Folder 152-154)
  - President's Discretionary Fund Review Meetings, 1997-2004 (Box 18, Folder 155-159, Box 19, Folder 160)
  - Patient Communication and Quality of Care Initiative (Box 19, Folder 161-164)
  - Planning a Strategy for Improving Outreach to Low-Income Medicare Beneficiaries: Robert Friedland/Gerontological Society of America (#20000450), 1996, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 165-168)
  - Demography is Not Destiny, Revisited: Georgetown University/Robert Friedland (#20020499), 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 169-170, Box 20, Folder 171-173)
  - Association Between Functional Health Literacy and Communication on Patient Safety in an Underserved Pediatric Population: Janet Serwint/Johns Hopkins Hospital (#20030680) (Box 20, Folder 174)
  - Addressing the Language Gap in Medicaid and State Children's Health Insurance Programs: Shelly Gehshan/ National Conference of State Legislatures (#20030731) (Box 20, Folder 175)
  - Improving Communication and Quality of Care for Limited English Proficiency Individuals: Developing Promising Practices: Mara Youdelman/National Health Law Program (#20030737) (Box 20, Folder 176)
  - To Better Understand Patients' Perceptions of the Role Race and Ethnicity Play in Establishing Open Communication Between Patients and Physicians of Different Races When Both Speak English: JudyAnn Bigby/Brigham and Women's Hospital (#20030753) (Box 20, Folder 177)
  - National Standards of Practice for Interpreters in Health Care: Cynthia Roat/National Council on Interpreting in Health Care (#20030797) (Box 20, Folder 178)
  - Examining Barriers to Improving Communication in the Health Care System: Robert Friedland/Georgetown University (#20030798) (Box 20, Folder 179)
  - The Language Factor in Patient Safety: Assessing the Nature and Preventability of Adverse Events for Minorities with Low English Proficiency: Andrew Chang/Joint Commission on Accreditation of Healthcare Organizations (#20030862) (Box 21, Folder 180)
  - Cultural Mastery – Leadership Models for Delivering Compassionate, Quality Care to Limited English Proficient Populations: Charlotte Collins/George Washington University (#20030868) (Box 21, Folder 181)
  - Communications and Cultural Competency Training for Healthcare Professionals Serving American Indians and Alaska Natives: Pamela Iron/National Indian Women's Health Resource Center, Inc. (#20030888) (Box 21, Folder 182)
  - Learning from Early Adoptors: Improving Patient Safety through Informed Consent in Limited English Proficiency/Low Literacy Populations: Elaine Power/The National Quality Forum (#20030894) (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - PALS for Health Program: Heng Foong/Special Services for Groups, Inc. (#20030900) (Box 21, Folder 184)
    PALS - Pacific Asian Language Services
  - Physician Incentives to Increase National Guideline Use on the Quality of Care Provided to a Managed Medicaid and State Children's Health Insurance Program (SCHIP) Population with Asthma: Susan McClair/Santa Barbara Regional Health Authority (#20030968) (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Beyond Language: Parent-Provider Discordance and Medical Errors During the Transition from Hospital to Home: Lauren Smith/Boston Medical Center (#20031057) (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - Quality, Safety, and Hospital Care for Latino Children: Addressing Parent and Provider Communication Challenges: Lisa Simpson/All Children's Hospital (#20031137) (Box 22, Folder 187)
  - Safety and Communication in Pediatric Cancer Care: Elisa Sobo/Center for Child Health Outcomes (#20031182) (Box 22, Folder 188)
- Program Officer Grant Files
  - Healthy Steps for Young Children Program: National Evaluation: Working Paper Series: Volume 1, Number 7, October 1, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 189)
  - Healthy Steps for Young Children Program: National Advisory Committee Meeting, October 18-19, 2001: Briefing Book (Box 22, Folder 190)
  - Healthy Steps for Young Children Program: "Healthy Steps for Iowa: Stepping in the Right Direction?", Susan Kinzer, March 2002 (Box 22, Folder 191)
  - Disability as a Predictor of Costs of Care in Older Women: Linda Fried/Johns Hopkins University (#980843), 1998-2002 (Box 22, Folder 192)
  - Helping Pediatricians Gauge Parental Concerns and Child Development: Michael Regalado/Cedars-Sinai Medical Center (#990567), 1999-2005 (Box 22, Folder 193, Box 23, Folder 194-201)
  - The Financial Implications of Modifying or Eliminating the Asset Test for Medicaid Assistance to Low-Income Medicare Beneficiaries: Robert Friedland/Gerontological Society of America (#990907), 1999-2002 (Box 23, Folder 202)
  - Medicare Facts and Faces: Diane Archer/Medicare Rights Center (#20000077), 1999-2001 (Box 23, Folder 203)
  - Prescription Drug Coverage in Retirement Health Plans: Jon Gabel/Health Research and Educational Trust (#20000260), 1999-2002 (Box 24, Folder 204)
  - Improving Program Outreach to Low-Income Medicare Beneficiaries, Phase One: Robert Friedland/Gerontological Society of America (#20000450), 1999-2002 (Box 24, Folder 205-206)
  - ICF (Barth) (#20010115) (Box 24, Folder 207)
  - Monitoring the Impact of the Medicare+Choice Program on the Elderly, Phase Three: Brian Biles/George Washington University(#20010123), 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 208-211)
  - 2001 Update of the Medicare+Choice Benefit and Premium Database: Marsha Gold/Mathematica Policy Research, Inc. (#20010156), 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 212)
  - Creating an Electronic Clinical System to Promote Child Development in Pediatric Practice: Raymond Sturner/Johns Hopkins University (#20010237), 2000-2005 (Box 25, Folder 213-219, Box 26, Folder 220)
  - Helping Pediatricians Gauge Parental Concerns and Child Development: Michael Regalado/Cedars-Sinai Medical Center (#20010574) (Box 26, Folder 221)
  - Contract #20010645: ICF Consulting/Michael Barth, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 222)
  - Evaluating Patients' Experience with Care Received from Primary Care Physicians: A Demonstration Project: Melinda Karp/Massachusetts Health Quality Partners, Inc.(#20010648), 2001-2006 (Box 26, Folder 223-227, Box 27, Folder 228-230)
  - Healthy Steps for Young Children Long Term Follow-up Study: Johns Hopkins University/Bernard Guyer (#20010683), 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 231-232)
  - Estimating Out-of-Pocket Costs Under Medicare+Choice: Marsha Gold/Alan Mittermaier/Mathematica (#20010685), 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 233)
  - Quality Measures for Children's Health Care: State of the Science: MGH/Anne Beal (#20020746) (Box 27, Folder 234)
  - Healthy Steps National Evaluation, Phase Three, Year Five – Final Report: Johns Hopkins University/Bernard Guyer (#20020104) (Box 27, Folder 235)
  - Evaluating an Intervention to Promote Child Development for Vulnerable Young Children and Families: Columbia University/Kathryn McLearn (#20020183), 2001-2005 (Box 27, Folder 236, Box 28, Folder 237-240)
  - Analysis and Dissemination of Findings from the National Survey of Early Childhood Health (NSECH): University of California at Los Angeles/Neal Halfon (#20020383), 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 241-242)
  - A National Survey of U. S. Physicians about the Quality of Health Care: Kinga Zapert/Harris Interactive, Inc.(#20020414), 2001-2003 (Box 28, Folder 243-245, Box 29, Folder 246-247)
  - Building State Medicaid Programs' Capacity to Provide Child Health and Developmental Services, Phase Four: National Academy for State Health Policy/Patricia Riley (#20020418) (Box 29, Folder 248-250)
  - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD) – Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase Three: New York University/Carolyn Berry (#20020419) (Box 29, Folder 251)
  - Evaluation of North Carolina's "Assuring Better Child Health and Development " (ABCD) Initiative: North Carolina/Sherry Hay (#20020428) (Box 29, Folder 252)
  - Evaluation of a Healthy Steps Residency Training Program: University of Illinois/Leo (Jerry) Niederman (#20020445), 2002, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 253-255)
  - Enhancing Child Development Services in Medicaid Managed Care: Center for Health Care Strategies/Karen Brodsky (#20020487) (Box 30, Folder 256)
  - Estimating the Cost and Impact of Improved Nurse Staffing in Hospitals: Jack Needleman/Harvard School of Public Health (#20020510), 2001-2004 (Box 30, Folder 257-260)
  - Building More Effective Early and Periodic Screening, Diagnosis, and Treatment (EPSDT) Child Development Services for Washington State Medicaid Children: State of Washington/Douglas Porter (#20020590) (Box 30, Folder 261)
  - Utah's Early Childhood Development and Education for Medicaid Children: Utah Department of Health/Michael Deily (#20020591) (Box 30, Folder 262)
  - Building State Medicaid Capacity to Provide Child Development Services: State of Vermont/Paul Wallace-Brodeur (#20020592) (Box 31, Folder 263)
  - Impact of the Leapfrog Group's Intensive Care Unit Physician Staffing Standard: Peter Pronovost/Johns Hopkins University (#20020637) (Box 31, Folder 264)
  - Developing Two Additional Sections of the "Chartbook on Health Care Quality in the U.S." – Quality of Care of the Elderly and Quality of Care of Children: Sheila Leatherman/University of North Carolina (#20020658), 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 265-268)
  - Building a State Learning Network to Improve Measurement of Child Development Services: Foundation for Accountability/Christina Bethell (#20020694) (Box 31, Folder 269)
  - Overview of Key Findings from Healthy Steps Evaluations: Michael Barth/ICF Consulting (#20020695) (Box 31, Folder 270-271)
  - A Learning Collaborative to Strengthen Innovative Models for Rewarding Quality: Sarah Callahan/Academy for Health Services Research and Health Policy (#20020699), 2002-2006 (Box 31, Folder 272-275, Box 32, Folder 276-277)
  - Preventive Health Care for Children – Utilization and Adherence to Recommendations: Mark Schuster/University of California at Los Angeles (#20020750) (Box 32, Folder 278)
  - Public Benefits Programs for the Elderly: Should Asset Tests be Used? Repeated? Documented?: Center on an Aging Society/Laura Summer (#20030059), 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 279)
  - Consultation and Analysis for Dr. K. McLearn's Research Entitled: Evaluating the Healthy Steps Program – Effects of a Pediatric Intervention to Promote Child Development for Low Income and Vulnerable Children and Families: Johns Hopkins University/Bernard Guyer (#20030197), 2002-2006 (Box 32, Folder 280)
  - Identifying Effective International Approaches to Child Health Care and Developmental Services: University of California at Los Angeles/Alice Kuo (#20030314), 2002-2007 (Box 32, Folder 281-284, Box 33, Folder 285)
  - Profiling Children's Developmental Problems and Health Care Needs: Child Trends, Inc./Brett Brown (#20030340), 2001-2005 (Box 33, Folder 286-290)
  - Language Barriers for Seniors in Medicare: Leighton Ku/Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (#20030375), 2002-2004 (Box 33, Folder 291)
  - Strengthening the Developmental Surveillance and Referral Practices of Child Health Care Providers: Paul Dworkin/Connecticut Children's Medical Center (#20030666), 2002-2006 (Box 34, Folder 292-296)
  - Health Care of Low Income Medicare Beneficiaries – New York Supplement: Tufts New England Medical Center, Inc./Dana Safran (#20031421) (Box 34, Folder 297)
  - Policy Symposium on Big Choices: The Future of Health Care for Older Americans: University of Texas/Kenneth Apfel (#20031434) (Box 34, Folder 298)
  - Office-Based Prevention of Child Behavior Problems: An Urban Extension Project: Ellen Perrin/Tufts New England Medical Center, Inc. (#20040124), 2002-2006 (Box 34, Folder 299)
  - Reexamining the Impact of Medicare's Two Year Waiting Period on Return to Work: Focus Groups: Arc of the United States/Henry Claypool (#20040238), 2002-2004 (Box 34, Folder 300, Box 35, Folder 301)
  - Analysis of Employer-Sponsored Preferred Provider Organizations: Medstat Group/William Marder (#20040288), 2003-2004 (Box 35, Folder 302)
  - Achieving Consensus on Best Office Practices in Well Child Care: Stanford University/David Bergman (#20040370), 2003-2007 (Box 35, Folder 303-306)
  - Assessing the Potential Impact of the Medicare Prescription Drug and Improvement Act of 2003 on Beneficiary Choices and Expenditures: The Urban Institute/Robert Berenson (#20040492) (Box 35, Folder 307)
  - Linking Pediatric Developmental Care to Community Resources: Rochelle Mayer/Amy Fine/Georgetown College (#20040548), 2004-2007 (Box 35, Folder 308-309, Box 36, Folder 310)
  - Conference on Evidence-Based State Pharmacy Benefit Management and the Transition to a New Medicare Drug Benefit: Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey/Kimberley Fox (#20040702), 2004-2005 (Box 36, Folder 311)
  - 2005 Health Policy Seminars and Congressional Staff Retreat: Alliance for Health Reform/Edward Howard (#20050089), 2004-2005 (Box 36, Folder 312-314)
  - Implications of Medicare Part-D Prescription Drug Coverage on Home and Community- Based Services Waiver Program: University of Maryland/Charles Milligan (#20050272), 2004-2005 (Box 36, Folder 315)